

Business-oriented Industrial Engineer, fluent in English, with a PG Diploma in Project Management and 7+ years of experience in sales and financial management in leadership roles and multicultural teams.

Currently, I am the Senior Project Manager for CAPEX investments in Argentina's largest wine manufacturer. Moreover, I am pursuing a Master's in Artificial Intelligence, and work as a College Professor of Statistics.

Convinced of making a transition to a cutting-edge company, I am seeking a challenging role where I can blend my newly adquired tech skills with my management background.

#### LANGUAGES AND TECH SKILLS

- ENGLISH (C1)PORTUGUESE (B2)
- FRENCH (B1)
   ITALIAN (B1)
- SOL
- PYTHON
- POWER BI



cristian.dam.marino@gmail.com

Mendoza, Argentina

in in/cristian-d-marino/

# **CRISTIAN MARINO**

# SR PROJECT MANAGER PURSUING MASTER'S IN AI INDUSTRIAL ENGINEER

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Senior Project Manager**

Oct 2023 - Today

#### FECOVITA| Argentina

- PMO Leader. Responsible for CAPEX portfolio management.
- Formulation, feasibility study, bidding, execution and final audit of projects,
- Presentation of Investment opportunities and funding proposals to the Board.
- Achievements: 5 pre-approved projects. Currently, under bidding,

#### **General Manager**

Sep 2020 - Sep 2023

#### Brunal SRL | Argentina

- Strategic direction and general management of my family's real state business.
- Responsible for property management, deals and contracts negotiations.
- Tenants and landlords management. Responsible for payments, collections and tax filings,
- Achievements: Cash flow and financial stability, tax payments reduction.

#### **VP of Finance and Legal**

Aug 2019 - Jul 2020

#### The AIESEC Foundation | Chile

- Responsible for overall legal, financial and audit management and strategy,
- Leader of 6 teams. Multiple stakeholders management. Representative of the Chilean office before the Finance Board of the Global Headquarters,
- Achievments: Renegotiation of 5 key contracts leading to 28% revenue growth. Increase of financial reserves of 450%. Decrease of collection time in 23 days.

#### VP of Sales and Customer Experience Aug 2018 - Jul 2019

### The AIESEC Foundation | Nicaragua

- Responsible for overall commercial, sales and CX management and strategy.
   Leader of 5 teams and a network of 60+ local volunteers, Representative of the Nicaraguan office before the CX Board of the Global Headquarters
- Achievements: Sales interannual growth of 56%. NPS increase of 1.5.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Master's in Artificial Intelligence (currently pursuing)

#### Universidad de Buenos Aires | Argentina (online)

 Degree focused on data analysis, machine learning, deep learning, computer vision, time series analysis, natural language processing and big data.

#### **Project Management - Postgraduate Diploma**

2023

#### Universidad Nacional de Cuyo | Argentina

• Waterfall, hybrid and agile project management (PMI & Agile methodologies).

#### **MEng in Industrial Engineering**

2022

#### Universidad Nacional de Cuyo | Argentina

• Exchange programs in Chile and Bolivia. Volunteering experience in Brazil.